<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sunny Mordor</string>
    <string name="featured">Featured</string>
    <string name="generalInfo">General Info</string>
    <string name="visiting">Visiting</string>
    <string name="livingHere">Living Here</string>

    <string name="sponsors">Sponsors</string>

    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="geography">Geography</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>

    <string name="travelling">Travelling</string>
    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="lodging">Lodging</string>
    <string name="additionalInfo">Additional Information</string>

    <string name="careers">Careers</string>
    <string name="housing">Housing</string>

    <string name="infoImage">Information Image</string>

    <string name="myInfos">myInfos</string>
    <string name="myGotos">myGotos</string>

    <string name="sunnyMordor">Visit Middle-earth&#8217;s hottest new vacation spot.\n\n
        Enjoy all Mordor has to offer from invigorating hikes through the Dead Marshes to mountain
        biking down Mount Doom.\n\n
        Come for the grog, stay because you have no choice.
    </string>

    <string name="butcher">Klogg&#8217;s Butcher Shop\n\n
        www.hobbitsforlunch.com\n\n
        Meat&#8217;s back on the menu boys.</string>
    <string name="nazgulAir">Fly Nazgul Air&#8230;daily non-stop flights&#8230;because one does not
        simply walk into Mordor.\n\n
        (10% discount for all hobbits, must declare all valuables prior to boarding)</string>
    <string name="preciousTours">Personalized tourses of Mordor.  We shows it around&#8230;and then
        we eats it!!  No, no, no, we wouldn&#8217;t do that precious.\n\n
        It books its tour now at PreciousTourses.com</string>

    <string name="history1">Mordor&#8217;s past has been quite turbulent, impacted heavily by
        aggressive economic and territorial sanctions by the colonialistic nations of western
        Middle-Earth. Mordor has suffered heavily under the weight of illegally imposed war
        reparations which challenge its right to sovereign rule.</string>
    <string name="history2">In 2460, the Great Lord Sauron returned to power, touting his &#8220;Make
        Mordor Great Again&#8221; campaign. Investing heavily into Mordor&#8217;s infrastructure and
        defensive capabilities, the region&#8217;s unemployment rate dropped to an all-time low of
        -25%.  This was also a time of strong governmental support for the arts (well, ok, the
        Black Arts).</string>

    <string name="geography1">Warmed by the ever-present heat of Mount Doom, Mordor enjoys atypically
        warm weather all year long.</string>
    <string name="geography2">Massive mountain ranges to the North, West and South offer natural
        protection from aggressive neighboring nations for the peace-loving citizens of Mordor.</string>
    <string name="geography3">In the South, the Sea of Nurnen is a popular vacation destination and
        retirement spot.</string>

    <string name="blackSpeech">Black Speech is the national language of Mordor, with a heavy Orcish
        accent, sounding remarkably like Cockney. Some useful phrases to learn :\n\n
        Akhoth!!\nYes, Sir!!\n\n
        Amut alai&#8217;aaps throquuz?\n
        What kind of meat did I eat?\n\n
        Nar-azatizish!\n
        Don&#8217;t kill me!</string>

    <string name="passes">Many passes through the mountainous borders of Mordor are available for
        travel, including Cirith Gorgor, Cirith Ungol and the Morgul Pass.\n\n
        Please note that security
        on these paths is quite heavy so make sure you have current identification on you at all
        times as well as adequate currency for sanctioned guard appeasement fees.</string>

    <string name="palace">Barad-dur\n\n
        The royal palace is a popular attraction.  Free admission on the second Thursday of each month\n\n
        Visible from all of Mordor, just follow the big red eye.</string>
    <string name="blackGate">Morannon, the Black Gate\n\n
        Probably the largest, blackest gate you will ever see, spanning all of
        Cirith Gorgor.\n\n
        Arrive early to avoid long lines.</string>
    <string name="mountDoom">Mount Doom\n\n
        Trek to the top of this natural wonder for an unbeatable view of Mordor or visit the Crack
        of Doom to see actual lava flows.\n\n
        (Sorry, no hobbits allowed at this attraction at this time.)</string>

    <string name="honeymoonSuite">Barad-Dur Honeymoon Suite\n\n
        Spare no expense for a once-in-a-lifetime (possibly quite literally) stay at the palace of
        Lord Sauron himself.  Brad and Angelina stayed here and you can too.</string>
    <string name="overlook">Overlook Hotel\n\n
        For those seeking a little more seclusion, the Overlook Hotel, high in the mountains is
        perfect for a quiet escape.  Nothing like a little peace and quite to help you really get
        in touch with yourself.</string>
    <string name="shelob">Shelob&#8217;s Lair\n\n
        For those of you with a stricter budget, this no frills location is the perfect choice. It
        may not be the cleanest place to rest your head and you may have to put up with a few
        cobwebs, but the price cannot be beaten.\n\n
        Be sure to stay for breakfast, just not as breakfast.</string>

    <string name="noPhotos">In some areas, especially near the Black Gate, photographing military
        installations, government buildings, or even transport infrastructure can get you in trouble.
        If in doubt, cautiously and politely ask an orc captain, while trying not to smell too tasty.</string>
    <string name="noJokes">The invasion by the Last Alliance of Elves and Men is still a sensitive
        and painful matter for most Mordorians, and should not be talked about in a jesting manner.
        Similarly, save your orc jokes for when you get home. They have heard the jokes before, and
        don&#8217;t find them particularly humorous or endearing.</string>
    <string name="pointyHat">If you a meet an elderly chap with a big grey beard and a pointy hat,
        ignore everything he says. He will try to make you do something dangerous. He is quite
        persistent, so if he gets too annoying, feed him to a Balrog\n\n
        He may reappear a few weeks
        later looking all white and shiny, but don&#8217;t be deceived as he will try to make you kill
        yourself again.</string>

    <string name="army">There are many career opportunities in Mordor for a young entrepreneur. You
        can become a soldier in the army, or a standard-bearer in the army, or cook for the army, the
        possibilities are endless.\n\n
        Sign-on bonuses available for those who have their own sharp, pointy stick.</string>
    <string name="caves">There is no shortage of places to claim as your own, from large spacious
        caverns to small, cozy holes in the ground.</string>
</resources>
